[{"answer": "Good evening, Piers.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "How are you governor?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "I'm very well.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well probably he's the better one to answer that question, but I think that it's more and more apparent to the American people and I think to the Republicans who are paying attention to the American people that we want stuff done, that we want solutions.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "How does he play that tricky line?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well I think there's a different kind of dynamic that Speaker Boehner has to deal with.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Does the president have that kind of relationship with John Boehner, say, where we can feel optimistic that they're going to have a very different kind of relationship that can actually be more effective?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "I think it would be a disgrace to the memory of the tragedy in Newtown if the Congress was unwilling to deal with the causes of Newtown and tragedies like it too numerous to name.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "How can he overcome that kind of rather dispiriting negativity?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think you know I feel very strongly that we should grow a backbone, that we have to stand up for what we believe in.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "is it time that I think particularly for the Democrats in the Senate worried about losing their seats if they stand up to the NRA, is it time for a bit of moral fiber, a bit of political courage rather than cowardice in relation to the NRA?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Piers, thank you for the invitation, but I don't have announcements tonight.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Do you want to put your firm denials in right away as get it out of the way?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Nice try, Piers.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Can you make a statement along the lines of I have absolutely no desire to ever be president, just so I know you're probably quite interested?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I think that's the real point.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Do you wish perhaps that today's politicians from the president down showed some of the moral courage that Lincoln showed over the issue of slavery, for example?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well and Sunday we're going to do the at a White House ceremony.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "So explain to me what happens if it falls on a Sunday?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "A group of historians, including Doris, we meet periodically, a few times now at the White House and have what we call a historians' dinner, and talk to President Obama.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "And I understand you met with President Obama recently?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Well when you think about the great presidents, usually like old Abigail Adams once said, great necessities call forth great leaders.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "How do you rate President Obama in the pantheon of great presidents, or just presidents?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, remember, a point of history is to remind us our own times aren't uniquely oppressive.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "We need to get back to that?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, I think the most important thing about, not just Abraham Lincoln, but FDR or Teddy Roosevelt, is when a president looks back at history, they can learn from the stories, and the triumphs and the failures of previous presidents, which mean they're not just walking in there alone.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "And what would the answer be?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": ": Well not too heavy a heart, I will say.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Margaret, let me start with you, obviously heavy heart I should imagine, watching a Democratic president about to make his second inaugural speech, but what has he got on his plate, the president, which he needs to deal with in the second term?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well the first thing every president has to be careful of in a second term is, as Margaret alluded to, is overreach, misinterpreting your mandates.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "What are the big challenges for him in the second term?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well the president has been pretty clear this time on a couple of measures.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "How does he somehow get through this impasse with the Republicans who are still seething about him winning again, and were pretty successful frankly in thwarting him in his first term?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Look, it did work.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Are they right?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "But there are things that he can do through his leadership that could stimulate the economy, the economy and corporate tax reform, corporations -- their outreach to business leaders.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "And if it doesn't recover soon, President Obama won't have much wiggle room really on the economy, will he?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question, the two big triumphs that you can't just argue, one, he saved the economy from going into a depression when he first came into office.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "What has been his big triumphs and his big failures do you think?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Look, I'm not a general.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "What would you have done in Benghazi in the aftermath?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Look, as a person who reads the papers just like you, you and I both know that the guy who was there on the ground, who was putting on his social media line by line at the time line of the attack, was in custody in a neighboring country until just a couple of weeks ago.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Wait a minute, you said I went from naught to 60, what's the middle ground between taking action and not taking action?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "You round up the people who are responsible and you hold them responsible.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "The question is, what do you do after the assassination of an ambassador?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I'm not a general.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "You don't take military action?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I'm great, great.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Well, the way to do it is to aim to defeat them, not contain them.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "How do you take on that organization in the most efficient, smart way?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "So, the Arab spring, we're already seeing the fallout, in some areas, like what's happening in Mali, because a lot of those fighters came from Libya.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What is the threat in real terms from Iran, from North Korea, and indeed from the fallout from the Arab spring, do you think?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "North Korea may very well launch another nuclear test.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "And North Korea, do you see that as a real threat?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "They're in bed.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "And is the biggest challenge not a military one or the threat of being attacked but the relationship with China going forward in terms of America's ability to recover economically, is it time that they got into bed more with the Chinese?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Should Obama make that a priority?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I think it's really interesting.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Are you encouraged by John Kerry's appointment as secretary of state?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I've been of optimistic from the beginning.", "docId": "130119pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Are you encouraged -- just finally, are you encouraged, optimistic by where the Arab spring may go this year or are you quite pessimistic?", "qSentId": 499}]